[♪♪♪]
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[EERIE WHEEZING]
[♪♪♪]
[ON VIDEO]
KIDS: SpongeBob SquarePants!
BURGER BEARD: Ready?
BURGER BEARD & KIDS: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants,
SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants. ♪
[BURGER BEARD LAUGHING ON VIDEO]
[IN OTHER ROOM]
MARTY: I don't understand
what you're talking about.
What is this break?
Like, I-I... I'm here
as often as I can be.
I'm working two jobs.
I don't know what else
you want me to do.
[ON VIDEO]
Ah, what a wonderful day.
[SARAH & MARTY ARGUING INDISTINCTLY IN OTHER ROOM]
[ON VIDEO] The sun is out.
The water is shimmering.
Scallops are chirping.
So peaceful.
Good morning to you, sir.
Would you care to blow a bubble?
[DOOR CLOSES]
[EERIE WHEEZING, HEAVY BREATHING]
[PROGRAM CONTINUES, DISTORTED & INDISTINCT]
[♪♪♪]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
- [PHONE BUZZING]
- [GASPS]
[CONTINUES BUZZING]
[SIGHS]
[FLOORBOARDS CREAKING]
[DOOR CREAKING]
[HISSES, MAKES EXPLOSION SOUND]
[QUIET TAPPING]
[♪♪♪]
[ELECTRICAL HUMMING]
[LIGHT CLINKING]
- [LIGHTS CLINKING]
- [GASPS]
[QUIET, SHUDDERING BREATHS]
[QUIET THUMP]
- [TREMBLING BREATHS]
- [HEAVY THUMPING]
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
[PANTING HEAVILY]
- [HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
- [GASPING]
[WHIMPERING]
[FOOTSTEPS GROWING CLOSER]
- [WHIMPERING, PANTING]
- [CREAKING]
[OBJECTS SCRAPING ON FLOOR]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[DEEP, HEAVY CREAKING]
[HYPERVENTILATING]
[WHIMPERS]
[DEEP CREAKING]
- [RATTLING, CREAKING]
- [WIND WHISTLING]
[SQUEAKING]
- [SCREAMS]
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[SOBBING]
Oliver.
We're okay. We're okay.
What happened? Huh?
Can you use your words, please?
[OLIVER CONTINUES SOBBING]
There you go.
[AUTOMATED VOICE OVER SPEAKER]
Something.
In.
House.
Something in house.
That was probably
just a nightmare,
'cause there is nobody
in the house
- but your mom and your dad.
- [WHIMPERING]
All right, come here.
Come here, come here, come here.
Can you take some deep breaths
for me, huh?
Okay? We're gonna do
some deep breaths.
- Okay?
- [WHIMPERING STOPS]
[BOTH TAKING DEEP, SLOW BREATHS]
[♪♪♪]
SARAH: So, he woke up in the
middle of the night screaming.
I went in there.
I was up for two hours with him.
[SIGHS]
He's a little boy.
- He has nightmares.
- That's easy for you to say.
You never go in with him.
It's always me.
[CHUCKLING]
I slept through it.
- All right? I'm sorry.
- No, don't do that.
Why can't you just admit
that you don't want to help?
I help, okay?
I always help... when I'm awake.
- Hey, buddy.
- [PROGRAM PLAYING OVER PHONE]
No more nightmares, huh?
I heard you had
a bad dream, bud.
Need a hug?
I know what the problem is.
[DEVICE BEEPS]
Too far away.
Yep. Let's see.
Ten feet. Oh, that's definitely
too far for a hug.
What do you think five feet is?
Yeah, okay.
Little closer.
I'm getting the weirdest
reading on this thing.
It just...
[YELLS]
- Tummy tickles!
- [LAUGHING]
Ooh!
[BRITISH ACCENT]
Your throne, sire.
SARAH: Are you able to make it
to his speech therapy today?
[NORMAL VOICE]
MARTY: Oh, sorry, I can't.
Uh, I picked up a shift
at the parking lot.
SARAH: Oh, well, hopefully,
you can make one soon, right?
MARTY: Yeah, for sure.
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Are.
We.
Moving.
Are we moving?
You are not moving anywhere, okay?
So don't worry.
MR. CALARCO: Today, we're gonna start in
with multiplying more than two numbers.
- GIRL: Not cool, man.
- [STUDENTS GROANING, GRUMBLING]
You don't even know
what you're groaning about.
It's not so hard.
If you can multiply
two numbers, you can multiply three.
You just take it...
Make sure you pay attention
to the lesson, okay?
MR. CALARCO: Anybody want to take this?
Come on, you learn by trying.
Nobody?
Oliver.
What do you make
of these three numbers?
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
The.
Answer.
Is.
Eight.
- [STUDENTS LAUGHING]
- The answer is eight.
MR. CALARCO: Not quite.
I see what you did there, though.
You were adding
instead of multiplying.
Very good try, Oliver.
Anyone else
want to give it a go?
Go ahead, Byron.
How come Oliver still gets
to use his phone in class
but you took mine away?
He's autistic, dude.
So he gets special treatment?
MR. CALARCO: Oliver gets to use his phone
because he wasn't playing
Fortnite
during the Pledge of Allegiance.
- [LAUGHTER]
- STUDENTS: Ooh.
MR. CALARCO: Let's get back to our first pair.
The product of two and four...
why don't we start there?
[ON VIDEO]
SQUIDWARD: Try one of those
radioactive sludge balls you call food?
Next, I suppose you'll want me
to go square-dancing with Patrick.
MATEO: Hey. What's up?
SPONGEBOB: Sorry, Patrick.
MATEO: Do you want to come hang out with us?
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Where?
Oh, uh, it's just...
I saw something cool over there.
[♪♪♪]
That way.
I'll catch up in a sec.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS IN DISTANCE]
[♪♪♪]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[BIRDS CAWING]
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Friends.
[QUIET CREAKING]
Hello?
- [GASPS]
- Hey.
ZACH: I can't believe he actually fell for it.
- BYRON: Of course he did.
- [OLIVER MOANING QUIETLY]
- He's such a loser.
- ZACH: Is he having
- a heart attack?
- MATEO: He totally is.
We're supposed to call 911.
ZACH: Dude, dude, listen.
That's just how he talks.
- Moaner Boner.
- [LAUGHTER]
[VOICE FADING]
It's like, he can't even talk.
- [DISTORTED LAUGHTER]
- [GROWLING]
ZACH: Exactly. Hey, maybe he's a robot under his skin.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Moaner Boner thinks he's special.
- [DISTORTED CHATTER]
- [WHEEZING]
BYRON: Oh, did you want
to say something?
I can't believe you used to be
friends with
Moaner Boner over here.
- My mom made me.
- [AUTOMATED VOICE] You.
[DISTORTED]
I didn't want to.
- [AUTOMATED VOICE] Are.
- [snarling]
Very.
[KIDS LAUGHING]
You are very ugly.
[GASPS]
BYRON: Who's ugly now?
[WHIMPERING QUIETLY]
Come on.
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
[WHIMPERS QUIETLY]
[WHIMPERING LOUDLY]
SARAH: I didn't know
what to think when I pulled up
and he wasn't there
waiting for me.
I went right into
the worst-case scenarios.
Uh, did he get in trouble?
Did someone take him?
And then I found him
just screaming in the field.
That sounds very scary
for both of you.
And he lost his phone somehow.
I wish he could explain
what happened.
Good.
Now we're gonna try
using our words.
"Lost...
in field."
We're gonna work
on your F's, okay?
F's can be tricky.
"Field."
"Field." Can you try that?
F...
Oliver, you can do it.
DR. ROBYN: Okay.
Good practicing.
Have you been
trying to provide him
with social experiences,
like we discussed?
Poor guy still doesn't have
any friends.
You said he was hanging out
with your friend's son?
- Jennifer's son, Byron.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, w-we're not close anymore.
- Okay.
So, if you can make any effort
to help him find friends...
take him to birthday parties,
anything...
it can be a good way
to get him to open up.
And just like he's trying
to get better at talking,
we have to make sure
we're listening.
[DEVICES WHOOSHING SOFTLY]
[ON VIDEO]
Okay, Patrick, it's all in the technique.
First, go like this.
Spin around. Stop.
Double-take three times.
- One, two, three.
- SARAH: Come on.
Oliver, you got to stay
with me, okay?
[SNIFFS]
[DEVICE WHIRRING]
Five bucks, please.
Thanks a lot.
[CHAIR WHIRS]
[CHAIR WHIRS, CLACKS]
Come on.
- [CHAIR CLACKING]
- [GRUNTS]
[CHAIR CREAKING]
[QUIET TAPPING]
[LIGHT CLICKS, BUZZES]
[METALLIC SCREECHING]
- [GASPS]
- [WIND WHISTLING]
[GRUNTS, PANTS]
[LIGHT BUZZING]
[♪♪♪]
[WIPING HANDS]
[SIGHS]
[CRUNCHING]
- [WOMAN LAUGHING]
- [GASPS, SIGHS]
[MARTY PANTING]
[CHUCKLES]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[OLIVER LAUGHING]
SARAH: Oliver, take that box off.
MARTY: Whoa, buddy.
SARAH: It's time to brush your teeth.
- [OLIVER LAUGHING]
- [TV PLAYING QUIETLY]
SARAH: He's full of energy tonight.
MARTY: Yeah, he is.
Where'd you get that?
MARTY: It was at the lost and found at work.
I think it just
needs to be charged.
- I guess you like it, huh?
- [OLIVER CONTINUES LAUGHING]
Hey, be careful with the screen.
It's a little cracked.
- What?
- You know what.
I run around
with our son all day,
and you get to swoop in
and be the hero once again?
The hero?
[ARGUMENT CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
[ARGUMENT CONTINUES IN DISTANCE]
[TAKING DEEP BREATHS]
[SIGHS]
It's not all presents
and tummy tickles with me
like it is with you.
I just wish I could take
that part of him
and put it in a box
and tape it up
and hide it somewhere
so he didn't have to deal
with it.
Then he wouldn't be our Oliver.
I should've...
I should've taken him sooner.
What if he never learns to talk
because I didn't
- do anything for so long?
- No.
We didn't do anything.
He's never looked me in the eyes.
Do you know what it's like
for your own child
to never look you in the eyes?
Well...
[SIGHS]
he's got nice eyes,
if that helps.
No, Marty, it doesn't help,
because he... he loves you
and he hates me.
[SNARLS QUIETLY]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[GROWLS PLAYFULLY]
[MOANS SOFTLY]
[SNARLS]
[QUIET CRUNCHING]
[QUIET WHEEZING]
[CRUNCHING]
[♪♪♪]
[CRUNCHING CONTINUES]
- [DRYER BUZZES IN DISTANCE]
- [GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
[CHUCKLING QUIETLY]
[GASPS]
[QUIET CRUNCHING]
[SHRIEKING]
[♪♪♪]
[OLIVER WHIMPERS SOFTLY]
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
[FOOTSTEPS NEARBY]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[ON VIDEO]
Okay, now, how many of you
have played
musical instruments before?
Do instruments of torture count?
- No.
- Is mayonnaise an instrument?
No, Patrick, mayonnaise
is not an instrument.
[PROGRAM CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Is.
Dad.
Gone.
Is Dad gone?
Yes.
- Hello.
- [GASPS]
Who.
Are.
You.
Who are you?
- I am Larry.
- [GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
Your parents want you
to be normal.
I just want
to be your friend.
[OLIVER WHIMPERS SOFTLY]
SARAH: Hi, honey.
So, I just had a little chat
with Jennifer.
You know how Dr. Robyn's always
talking about
you making friends?
Well, we're gonna have
a sleepover this weekend.
I know it's scary.
I'm nervous, too.
I haven't really seen Jennifer
since that whole incident,
but can you try and have
some fun for me?
You noticed your dad's gone
earlier than usual, huh?
I have something
I need to talk to you about.
Um, I've been wanting
to talk to you about it
for a while, but I've just...
I haven't been sure what to say.
Your dad and I love you so much.
I don't want you to feel alone.
That's why we're gonna have
the sleepover this weekend.
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
Is that your way of saying
you don't want to talk to me
about it?
[DOOR SLAMS]
[LOW GROWLING]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[KNOCKING]
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Thank you for coming.
- Nice to see you.
- You, too.
So, I hope you're gonna be okay
with these guys.
They can be a little bit
of a handful.
Oh.
- Yeah, I think we'll be fine.
- [DOOR CLOSES]
Byron just felt more
comfortable with his posse.
- You're welcome to stay for a while.
- Oh.
And spend more time with Byron
than I have to?
- Mom.
- Yes.
I'm just kidding, honey.
- Not kidding.
- [BOTH CHUCKLE]
So, um, can I say hi?
Oh, yeah. Of course, yes.
Yeah.
[CHUCKLES]
Oliver.
You remember Jennifer, right?
- JENNIFER: Hi, Oliver.
- [SARAH CHUCKLES]
ZACH: Why does he do that
weird thing with his fingers?
- JENNIFER: Okay, be nice, guys.
- SARAH: No, it's okay. Um...
It helps calm him down.
- It's called stimming.
- ZACH: Okay.
But why?
Well, he's under-sensitive
to stimulation,
so sometimes he needs
to touch his own skin
or spin in a circle,
and it makes him feel good.
Can he spin forever
without puking?
SARAH: Sure seems like it.
[CHUCKLES]
That's kind of cool.
SARAH: Come on, Oliver.
JENNIFER: Hi, Oliver.
It's really nice
to see you, honey.
My gosh, you've gotten big.
SARAH: Yeah. Yeah, he's...
he's still not talking,
but his writing
has really improved.
- JENNIFER: That's awesome.
- SARAH: Mm-hmm.
JENNIFER: High five?
- [SARAH INHALES SHARPLY]
- Whoa. Still strong.
Okay, that is not gonna happen,
because he knows now
to keep his hands to himself.
- JENNIFER: Of course.
- SARAH: Right, Oliver?
JENNIFER: Well, the boys have
all agreed to include Oliver,
so I'm sure it's just gonna be
a really great night.
[♪♪♪]
[OLIVER MOANING SOFTLY]
[CONTINUES MOANING]
ZACH: Is he gonna make
those sounds the whole night?
BYRON: Keep it down.
[MOANING CONTINUES]
Isn't it sad that your mom
has to force kids
to come over and pretend
to be your friend?
MATEO: What are you staring at, anyway?
Moaner Boner's been looking
at that closet all night.
Maybe that's where he keeps
his secret candy stash.
What? Are you guys telling me
you don't have
a secret candy stash?
I'm gonna check it out.
MATEO: Do you see any candy?
- [OLIVER MOANS]
- Hey!
BYRON: What's your deal?
We all got these.
ZACH: Aw, does he think
we're gonna steal it?
Want to see what kind of games
you got on here.
[OLIVER PANTING]
- What's this?
- [OLIVER GRUNTS, MOANS]
Does your mommy still read you
bedtime stories?
"This is Larry."
ZACH: Who's Larry?
MATEO: Yeah, who's Larry?
This guy.
[CHUCKLING]
Whoa. Look at that dude.
ZACH: Yeah.
He looks just like your dad.
- MATEO: Shut up.
- [MOANS SOFTLY]
My dad is way hairier.
- [GASPS SOFTLY]
- BYRON: "Larry never gets to play pretend.
He gets made fun of
because he's different."
- [LIGHT CLINKING RAPIDLY]
- [GASPS]
Okay, did your parents
forget to pay
- the electricity bill?
- [MATEO CHUCKLING]
"Larry just wants a friend."
ZACH: Are you guys seriously
afraid of a dead light bulb?
[GASPING]
Two dead light bulbs.
[OLIVER MOANING]
[MOANING]
BYRON:
"He's tall and pale and thin
"and tries to hide his face.
"He isn't from
the world you know.
Larry comes from another place."
Uh, maybe we should
stop reading.
"Larry watches
through your windows,
"which connect
his realm to yours.
"He needs you to know
his whole story
to turn those windows
into doors."
What does that mean?
- [LIGHT BULBS POPPING]
- [KIDS SCREAMING]
- Oh, my God!
- Shit! Shit!
- [SCREAMING CONTINUES]
Oh, my God.
What's going on?
Oh, my God!
[SCREAMING]
- [KIDS SCREAMING IN DISTANCE]
- Oh, my God!
[ALL PANTING]
- [SWITCH CLICKING]
- [KIDS WHIMPERING, MUTTERING]
Come on.
[OLIVER MOANING]
[CRUNCHING]
[WHEEZING]
ZACH: Are you making those sounds, Moaner Boner?
[CLICKS]
[SLOW CRUNCHING]
[QUIET WHEEZING CONTINUES]
[SOFT CRUNCHING]
[TREMBLING BREATHS]
[SHAKILY]
ZACH: What the shit is that?
Shit.
Shit, shit, shit.
- [BONES CRUNCHING]
- [KIDS GASP]
- What the hell kind of app is this?
- Is it an app?
Should I read the next page?
I'm gonna read the next page.
No, no, no.
Don't read the next page.
BYRON: "Larry has looked
through the glass
"and found you staring back.
"He understands your loneliness.
"A true friend is what you lack.
Will you be Larry's friend?"
No! No, I will not
be Larry's friend.
Guys, guys, th-there's nothing
in the corner.
- No. No, no, no.
- No, no, no.
- No, no, no. No, no, no.
- Don't! No, don't!
- No, don't! Don't!
- [OLIVER MOANING]
- [OTHERS PANTING, MUTTERING]
See?
It's probably just a fuse.
Do you see him?
Do you see Larry?
BYRON: Guys, there's
no such thing as Larry.
It's just your imagination
playing tricks on you.
[YELLS]
[ALL SCREAMING]
What is happening?
Oh, my God!
Byron, are you okay?
[DISTRESSED MOANING]
SARAH: I don't know how this happened.
I don't see how Oliver
could've done this.
JENNIFER: Byron, baby?
Do you think you can tell us
what happened now?
MATEO'S DAD: Who did this?
It was... it was Oliver.
[SHUDDERING]
He's a freak.
- Excuse me?
- MATEO'S DAD: Let's go.
SARAH: Jennifer, I... I'm sorry.
I am so sorry.
We got to go.
[VEHICLE DOORS CLOSING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[PANTING]
[QUIET WHEEZING EXHALE]
- [SWITCH CLICKS]
- [GROANS]
How did you blow out
all of these lights?
I don't understand.
Were you trying
to hurt Byron again?
Not you?
Well, who else
could it have been?
You know, if you want friends,
you can't push furniture
into them.
[OLIVER HUMMING AN UPBEAT TUNE]
Will you at least help me
move this table?
- [TABLE DRAGGING]
- Please stop humming.
We are not happy right now.
This...
[HUMMING CONTINUES]
Is that the SpongeBob song?
[CONTINUES HUMMING THEME FROM SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS]
[HUMMING STOPS]
You don't...
you don't have to stop.
Does that help you calm down?
Maybe I pushed you
into this too fast.
We've got a lot going on
in this house,
and maybe we're just
not ready for friends.
[♪♪♪]
[DISTORTED]
MR. CALARCO: Let's fly on over
to the Midwestern region.
Which one is this?
North or South Dakota?
STUDENT: South Dakota.
MR. CALARCO: That's right.
Underneath South Dakota is...?
- STUDENT: Nebraska?
- MR. CALARCO: Nebraska.
Jade, what's under Nebraska?
JADE: Kansas.
MR. CALARCO: Kansas. Nice one.
Oliver, do you want
to give this one a try?
Oliver, did you bring
your talker today?
Another day.
MR. CALARCO: And under Kansas?
STUDENT: Oklahoma?
[SIGHS]
[QUIET TAPPING]
Misunderstood Monsters.
"This is Larry.
"Larry never gets
to play pretend.
"He gets made fun of
because he's different.
Larry just wants a friend."
[LIGHT CLINKING]
[LIGHTS CLINKING, CRACKLING]
[GRUNTS, GROANS]
[SPUTTERS]
[GROANS]
[GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
[TREMBLING BREATHS]
Marty?
[SLOW, HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
- [FOOTSTEPS CONTINUE]
- [CRUNCHING]
Hello?
- [CHAIR DRAGS]
- [GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
[FLOORBOARDS CREAKING QUIETLY]
Hello?
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Hello.
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
Is somebody watching me?
Oliver, what the hell
did you download on this thing?
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Say goodbye to Oliver.
Have you been talking to my son?
You need to stop.
This is not funny.
[♪♪♪]
Stay away from my son.
I won't let you hurt him.
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Not hurt.
Take.
[VOICE DISTORTING]
Take, take,
take, take, take, take.
[LIGHTS CLINKING]
[HEAVY FOOTSTEPS THUMPING QUICKLY]
[SARAH GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
MR. CALARCO: Why? To collect and...
- Everything okay?
- Sorry. Uh, Oliver?
- Is Oliver here?
- Yeah.
- [STUDENTS WHISPERING]
- Thank God you're all right.
We got to go.
We have a family emergency,
so we're just gonna go.
[♪♪♪]
We just got to get you home,
okay?
I know. I know this isn't
part of your routine.
It's just...
Someone was watching us at home.
They said they want to take you.
- [CELL PHONE RINGING]
- Oh.
Hi. Jen, I can't...
What do you mean,
he's not talking?
JENNIFER: I don't know what
they got up to this weekend,
but Byron,
he still hasn't slept.
Won't go to school.
Won't eat.
Two days with him not talking,
and... [SIGHS]
I seriously don't know
how you do it.
I think someone hacked
into Oliver's screen.
Someone was talking to me.
[CONVERSATION CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
SpongeBob, I just want
to say that I'm...
[SPUTTERING]
sorry.
What?
I'm trying to say I'm...
[BRAYING LIKE A DONKEY]
- [CHUCKLING]
- SPONGEBOB: What?
I mean, how could someone
use that to get to...
[PROGRAM CONTINUES OVER PHONE]
Honey, it's nice of you
to try and apologize,
but I don't think he wants
to watch SpongeBob right now.
It was Larry.
Honey?
Oliver didn't do anything.
It was Larry.
JENNIFER: Who's Larry?
I read about Larry today
in that story.
Tell me what you saw, please.
Larry just wants a friend.
H-He made the lights go out.
I-I could hear him in the house.
H-He moved things, but...
but I couldn't see him.
Not really.
JENNIFER: So, you guys played make-believe?
No.
[SIGHS]
He's the one that hurt me,
not Oliver.
Larry.
I could feel him.
His hands around my neck.
[SNARLING]
He tried to kill me.
[♪♪♪]
Larry just wants a friend.
[ECHOING]
[PANTING]
SARAH: Hurry! Oliver!
We got to get to Dad.
We can't stay here.
Honey, I'm sure it's nothing,
but better to be safe, right?
Can you look at me?
[MOANING SOFTLY]
We should get going, okay?
And no screens.
[♪♪♪]
- [DOOR BANGS, CREAKS]
- [GASPS]
- [LARRY WHEEZING]
- [HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
[GASPS QUIETLY]
[FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
[LARRY MOANS SOFTLY]
[CLINKING, ELECTRICAL BUZZING]
[LIGHTS CONTINUE CLINKING]
[HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
- [FOOTSTEPS STOP]
- [CRUNCHING]
[RUMMAGING]
[LARRY MOANING]
- SARAH: Oliver!
- [GASPS]
[LARRY GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
What are you talking about?
SARAH: I know it sounds crazy,
but I was reading this story
about Larry,
and then the lights...
they started going on and off.
And then another one
was going on and off.
It was like he was using
the electricity
to move around the room.
And then he screwed in
all the new light bulbs.
So, he helped you
with your chores.
[SHUDDERING BREATH]
He must have needed the power
or something to come alive.
- Larry?
- Larry.
I knew I shouldn't
have moved out.
I'm not making this up.
Oliver saw him.
There is something
inside our house.
O-Oliver, here.
Tell Daddy.
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
He.
Wants. Me.
As. Friend.
This thing wants our son.
Okay.
I think you need
a good night's sleep.
I'll take him to school
in the morning.
No, I am not letting him
out of our sight.
How do we know
the school is safe?
Okay, well, why don't I bring
him to work with me tonight
if he's not going
to school tomorrow?
Absolutely not.
Oh, come on. What, you don't
trust me with him?
No, it's not that. It's...
Rest is important for the body.
So, you sleep, and...
we can talk about
all this tomorrow.
- Really, come on.
- [SARAH SIGHS]
Let me take care of him.
[DEVICE WHIRS, CLICKS]
Give this and the change
to the gentleman.
There you go.
Thanks so much.
Have a good one.
My man is a pro!
Very nicely done.
See? Look how good
you are at that.
- You could take over for me some nights.
- [CHUCKLES]
The best part is that,
in between cars,
you can do whatever you want.
You can listen to the radio.
You can even watch SpongeBob.
Oh, hey.
- Ah. Is this the infamous haunted screen?
- [OLIVER MOANS]
It's okay.
Hey. Do you know how
your nightmares aren't real?
Well, neither are ghosts or
ghouls or vampires or witches,
and certainly not Larrys.
- [OLIVER GRUNTS]
- "This is Larry."
[RATTLING]
[RUSTLING NEARBY]
[CHUCKLING]
[TAKING DEEP BREATHS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[♪♪♪]
"Will you be Larry's friend?"
[LIGHTS BUZZING]
[TREMBLING BREATHS]
- It's nothing.
- [SETS TABLET DOWN]
Happens all the time.
- It's okay.
- [SWITCH CLICKING]
Huh.
Hang tight.
All right.
Let's see what we have here.
[DEVICE BEEPS]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[♪♪♪]
[OLIVER GASPS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[FOOTSTEPS CONTINUE]
[FOOTSTEPS WALKING FASTER]
- [SHUDDERING BREATHS]
- [FOOTSTEPS GROWING CLOSER]
[FOOTSTEPS RUNNING]
- [FOOTSTEPS STOP]
- [LARRY GROWLS]
[TREMBLING BREATHS]
[GASPS QUIETLY]
- [GASPS, YELPS]
- Oliver, what are you doing, buddy?
What if a car drove in? Huh?
You got to be more careful.
Hey. Here.
Give me this.
- Look. Hey.
- [OLIVER MOANING SOFTLY]
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Look.
Buddy, there's nothing.
Hey. Look at me.
Okay? There's nothing out there.
Okay? I'll show you. Look.
See?
Look at that.
- [OLIVER MOANS]
- [QUIET CRUNCHING]
[♪♪♪]
See?
[OLIVER WHIMPERS]
Totally safe.
- [CRUNCHING]
- Oliver!
- [LARRY SNARLING]
- Let him go!
[DOOR SQUEAKS OPEN]
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
I saw through that-that...
that screen
the way he was holding Oliver.
SARAH: Why does he want our son?
The story said something,
um, about, uh...
[STAMMERING]
"A true friend is what you lack."
He hasn't had a friend
since-since...
Oh, yeah, since Jennifer and I
got in our fight.
- I know.
- Yeah, some stupid fight.
Hey, Oliver hit Byron,
and then she decided
our son was dangerous.
Either way, he's been lonely
long before that.
I mean, Oliver's been staring
at his screens for years,
and that...
that thing has been
staring right back.
And how come
we can't see it, huh?
I-I don't know.
MARTY: Doesn't make any sense.
How-how can he be here
and not here at the same time?
SARAH: What have you got, honey?
- MARTY: That's very nice.
- [OLIVER SIGHS]
[SARAH GASPS SOFTLY]
[MARTY CHUCKLES]
We got some kid.
Larry's in his world,
and we're in ours, but...
- But we're also together.
- [SARAH SIGHS]
Larry can interact with us,
but he can't reach us.
He can't get to Oliver yet.
That's why he wants
to get into our world.
If that's his window...
Then we have to destroy it
before it becomes his door.
- [STRIKING, GLASS SHATTERING]
- [SARAH GRUNTING]
- [MARTY GRUNTS]
- [SARAH GRUNTS]
[MARTY AND SARAH PANTING]
[MARTY GRUNTS]
- [MUFFLED THUMP]
- [LARRY WHEEZING]
[MUFFLED THUMP]
[LARRY SQUEALS]
[MARTY & SARAH CONTINUE GRUNTING]
[OLIVER PANTING]
[LARRY WHIMPERING]
[LARRY SQUEALS]
DR. ROBYN: We have the cookie,
we have the blue car,
and you get to choose...
whichever one you want.
What's it gonna be?
[CHUCKLING]
Yeah. Good.
SARAH: Marty and I both experienced it.
It's not just
in Oliver's imagination.
I'll be right back, kiddo.
Sarah, do you know
what a physical empath is?
No.
It's when you love
someone so much
that you feel or experience
their pain.
It's a good sign.
It shows just how much
you care about Oliver.
And it's very common in parents.
So, you're saying that we could
be seeing his imagination
because we love him?
That doesn't make any sense.
But an invisible monster
that travels
through electricity does?
Well, we're hoping
that that's over now
because we destroyed that thing.
So, does he have a way
to communicate?
I'll...
let him take my phone
with him to school
until we can afford a new one.
Unless you could get him
talking first.
Sarah.
Come on, it's...
it's extremely rare
for kids his age
to start verbalizing in the way
I fear you're imagining.
[SIGHS]
I know. I know.
I just...
I just want to make sure
that you still have
the right expectations.
If he can say a few words...
maybe a sentence here or there...
that would be a big win.
We have to keep remembering
his strengths.
[♪♪♪]
Have you seen him again?
What's this?
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
He. Gave.
It. To. Me.
Seriously?
Yes.
Then Mom and Dad broke him.
Broke him?
S-So, like, he's gone, then?
Yes.
[BYRON SIGHS]
Can I ask you something?
Yes.
Why'd you stop being my friend?
We used to hang out
all the time.
I. Did.
Bad. Thing.
You did?
Punch. Face.
Your. Mom. Mad.
I barely even had a bruise.
The next day,
I was asking my mom
when we could have
another sleepover.
But she played me
a message from your mom.
Your mom said you didn't want
to be my friend anymore.
That is lie.
Wait.
So, you never said that?
Lie.
Wrong.
I never.
BYRON: Lie.
[LAUGHS]
Moms are so weird.
What are you watching
over there?
Wait.
Let me guess.
SpongeBob?
[♪♪♪]
[VEHICLE PASSES]
[SIGHS]
[TAPPING]
[♪♪♪]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
No.
[LIGHT CLUNKS]
[PANTING]
[SETS PHONE DOWN]
[ELECTRICAL WHIRRING]
- [ELECTRICAL WHOOSHING]
- [LIGHT CLICKS]
- [WHOOSHING]
[CAR ALARM BLARES]
- [LIGHT CLICKS]
[HORN HONKS TWICE]
[ALARM CHIRPING]
[ALARM BLARES, ENGINE STARTS]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[ALARM BLARES]
[TREMBLING BREATHS]
[GRUNTING]
No!
[GRUNTS]
- [HANDLE RATTLING]
- [GRUNTS, PANTS]
Help!
- Hello!
- [BANGING]
Somebody help!
- [QUIET CRUNCHING]
- [FAINT MOANING]
- [SLOW FOOTSTEPS]
- [GASPS]
[PANTING]
[FOOTSTEPS THUMPING]
[LARRY MOANING SOFTLY]
[FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
[PANTING]
[PHONE CLICKS]
[CRUNCHING]
[SHUDDERING BREATHS]
[MOANS SOFTLY]
[WHEEZING]
[FOOTSTEPS THUMPING]
[FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [LOUD CLANK]
[METALLIC CREAKING]
[RATTLING]
[CRUNCHING]
[SCREAMS]
- [BANGING]
- [LARRY SNARLS]
[WHIMPERS, YELLS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[♪♪♪]
[ELECTRICAL WHOOSHING]
[LOUD THUD]
[RATTLING, THUMPING]
Where are you?
No!
- Shit.
- [ENGINE REVS]
[WHIMPERING]
[ELECTRICAL WHOOSHING]
[PANTING]
[LARRY SNARLS]
- [SCREAMS]
- [TIRES SQUEAL]
- [WATER RUNNING]
- [PANS CLATTERING]
[WATER STOPS]
You need any help
with your homework?
Hey, I talked to Jennifer today.
She said Byron's doing
much better.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Hello?
How?
OFFICER: We found him in his
car on the side of the road.
We're not sure how it happened.
He was unresponsive.
W-We rushed him
to the hospital...
- [VOICE FADES, STATIC CRACKLES]
- Hello?
Hello?
[SIGHS]
Hello!
[LARRY MOANING OVER PHONE]
[GASPS]
[WHIMPERS]
- [LIGHT CLINKS]
- [GASPING]
[PANTING]
[ON TV]
Welcome to the Krusty Krab.
How may I help you?
- Yeah...
- Did you turn it on?
[ON TV] ...two large fries
and a Jumbo Krabby Patty.
SPONGEBOB: Hey! What's that?
[SPONGEBOB GIGGLING]
What are you doing
behind the counter?!
[STATIC CRACKLES OVER TV]
[GASPS]
- He...
- Will...
- Follow...
- You...
- Until...
- Finish...
- The...
- Story.
- [AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
Why are you doing this to us?
Where did you come from?
- World...
- Only...
- Look...
- At...
- Screens...
- Not...
Each other.
SARAH: What?
What does that mean?
- People...
- Very...
Lonely.
- All...
- That...
- Loneliness...
- In...
- World...
- Made...
Larry.
- Larry...
- Made...
- Of...
- Loneliness.
SARAH: Larry is lonely?
How do you think I would feel
if Larry took Oliver?
- Finish...
- The...
Story.
- Finish...
- The...
Story.
No.
- [TV CLICKING, CRACKLING]
- [GASPS]
SARAH: No, no, no, no.
SARAH: No. Stop. Stop.
[SARAH GASPS]
No. No!
- No.
- [OLIVER GASPING]
- [GRUNTS]
[YELLS]
[GASPING]
[GRUNTS]
[DISTRESSED GROANING]
[♪♪♪]
[ELECTRICAL WHOOSHING]
[GROANING INTENSIFIES]
[ELECTRICAL BUZZING]
[OLIVER CONTINUES GROANING]
Can you just be normal
for one second?
[GROANING STOPS]
[CRYING]
Oliver.
Oliver, I didn't mean it.
Honey.
Sometimes...
even moms and dads say things
that they shouldn't.
I just... I...
Your dad...
he's been in an accident,
and, um...
they're trying to wake him up.
Something happened to him,
and I think it was Larry.
And I cannot let Larry
get us, too.
[ELECTRICAL CLANKING & CRACKLING IN DISTANCE]
[ELECTRICAL CRACKLING & POPPING]
[ELECTRICAL WHIRRING]
Oh, my God.
[ELECTRICAL WHOOSHING]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[ENGINE WHINES BRIEFLY]
[LIGHTS TICKING]
[WHOOSHING]
[LIGHTS CLINKING]
- [WHOOSHING]
- [LIGHTS CLINKING]
[LIGHT CRACKLES, CLINKS]
[LIGHT BUZZING]
[WHOOSHING FADES]
[SARAH GASPS]
[ELECTRICAL HUMMING]
- [SNARLING]
- [SARAH GASPING]
- [SARAH SCREAMS]
[♪♪♪]
[LARRY MOANING OUTSIDE]
[FOOTSTEPS THUMPING]
[LARRY MOANS SOFTLY]
- [LARRY SNARLS]
- [GASPS]
[FOOTSTEPS THUMPING]
[WHISPERS]
Okay. Okay. Okay.
[FOOTSTEPS STOP]
- [FOOTSTEPS RESUME]
- [GASPS]
[FURNITURE DRAGGING]
[LARRY MOANS SOFTLY]
[LARRY SHRIEKS]
[WHISPERS]
We're gonna go for the door.
Stay quiet.
- [DOG BARKING]
- [LARRY GROWLS, SNARLS]
[♪♪♪]
[SNARLING]
[CLATTERING IN OTHER ROOM]
[WHISPERS]
Oliver.
If something happens to us...
...I don't want you to think
that I meant
what I said downstairs.
[FURNITURE DRAGGING IN OTHER ROOM]
What did I lie about?
Byron?
Oh, honey, I...
You hit him out of nowhere.
I thought it would be
easier for everyone
if I just cut ties.
"You took away...
"...friend.
"Now I...
go with..."
No. No, don't...
d-don't go with Larry.
You're right.
I did lie.
And I didn't do it...
Honey, I didn't do it
to protect you.
I did it to protect me.
Oliver.
Can you look at me, please?
Please, can you look at me?
It's okay.
I know you're listening.
You're always listening.
Much more than I listen to you.
[SLOW, HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
[TREMBLING BREATHS]
- [FOOTSTEPS CONTINUE]
- [OLIVER PANTING]
[WHIMPERS]
Oliver.
[OLIVER MOANS SOFTLY]
[LARRY WHEEZING]
[MOANS, PANTS]
[WHIMPERS]
Oliver.
- Hey.
- [OLIVER MOANING]
[SARAH HUMMING THEME FROM SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS]
[HUMMING ENDS]
[FOOTSTEPS THUMPING NEARBY]
[LARRY SNARLS]
[QUIET, TREMBLING BREATHS]
[RASPING]
LARRY: Oliver.
Come...
play.
[CLATTERING]
[PANTING QUIETLY]
[FOOTSTEPS THUMPING]
[FOOTSTEPS STOP]
[CRUNCHING]
[CREAKING]
[SNARLS]
[HEAVY CREAKING]
[LARRY MOANS]
[RASPING]
Friend.
- Friend...
- [ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
OLIVER: F...
- [SARAH SHUSHING QUIETLY]
- F...
- [SHUSHING]
Fie-ld.
Field, field, field, field.
Field, field, field,
field, field...
- [GROWLS]
- [SCREAMING]
[HISSING, SNARLING]
No! No!
Oliver!
[GRUNTS]
- [GASPS]
- [OLIVER GRUNTING]
[ELECTRICAL CRACKLING, HUMMING]
Field, field, field, field,
field, field, field, field.
Why the field?
[PANTING]
- [ENGINE STARTS, REVS]
- [SARAH GASPING]
- [ENGINE STARTS]
- [ALARMS WAILING, HONKING]
[WHIMPERING]
[YELLING, PANTING]
[YELPS]
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
[DISTANT ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
There's no electricity here.
He can't get us.
Hey.
Oh, you did it.
You did it.
You saved us.
Oh!
[SARAH CHUCKLING]
[ELECTRICAL HUMMING & CRACKLING]
[GASPS]
[TREMBLING BREATHS]
[ELECTRICAL WHIRRING]
[FAINT MOANING]
- [SNARLS]
- Run!
Run! Come on!
Run!
[PANTING]
[FRIGHTENED WHIMPERING]
[GRUFF PANTING]
[LARRY SHRIEKS]
[BOTH PANTING]
[SNARLS]
SARAH: Stop! No, Oliver!
No.
Oliver.
[DISTANT BIRDCALL]
Oliver!
[GASPING]
[SNARLS]
- No!
- [OLIVER SCREAMS]
[DISTRESSED GROANING]
SARAH: Oliver!
[LARRY & OLIVER PANTING]
[CRUNCHING]
[LARRY BREATHING SLOWER]
[LARRY BREATHING SLOWLY]
[♪♪♪]
[RASPING]
Friends.
[LEAVES RUSTLING IN WIND]
[♪♪♪]
[LARRY SNARLS]
[SHRIEKS]
I'll be your friend, Larry.
[GASPS]
We both want the same thing.
We both want to protect Oliver.
[OLIVER WHIMPERING]
[HISSES SOFTLY]
[OLIVER WHIMPERS, GASPS]
I love you.
I love all of you.
[♪♪♪]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[WHIMPERS]
[CRUNCHING]
[GROANING WEAKLY]
[WHIMPERING]
- [HIGH-PITCHED GROANING]
- [CRUNCHING]
- [OLIVER SOBS, GASPS]
- [SARAH SCREAMS]
[LARRY SNARLING]
- [LARRY GRUNTING IN DISTANCE]
- [PANTING]
[YELLS]
[YELLING]
[LARRY GROWLS]
[PANTS, WHIMPERS]
[WHIMPERS SOFTLY]
[♪♪♪]
[DISTANT ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
[DISTANT SIRENS, CAR ALARMS]
[SOBBING SOFTLY]
Good.
Now, you want to give it a try?
M...
Mom...
"Mom." Excellent.
Loves...
M...
Me.
Wonderful.
"Mom loves me."
I know for a fact
your mom loves you very much.
MARTY: You're so good with him.
[CHUCKLES]
So are you.
How's he doing at home?
[SIGHS]
He seems okay.
I've been trying to give him
more social experiences,
like you said.
Uh, we've been practicing his speech,
like, uh, five times a day.
Well, you don't want
to wear him out.
[CHUCKLES]
Let's say three times a day.
- Oh. Okay.
- [DR. ROBYN CHUCKLES]
Got it.
[SNIFFS]
Three times a day.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[QUIETLY]
For speech work.
[SIGHS]
[TAKES DEEP BREATH]
I mean, you know Sarah...
she was...
...incredible.
I thought I understood, but I...
I just wish I could tell her
that I'm sorry.
That I'm trying now.
I'm sure she'd like
to hear that.
I hope...
they'll find her.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[EXHALES]
Is that you?
[♪♪♪]
[LAUGHTER, PLAYFUL CHATTER]
- Hey.
Can I, uh...
eat lunch with you guys
tomorrow or something?
That depends.
Are you willing
to take the pledge?
What pledge?
A secret handshake.
For those of us
who've seen Larry.
The pledge to stay friends.
To play together forever.
So no one has to be alone
like Larry.
[♪♪♪]
[CLINKING, CRACKLING]
[LIGHTS CLINKING, CRACKLING]
[OLIVER LAUGHING]
[LAUGHING CONTINUES]
[MARTY GASPS]
- [PHONE CLICKS]
- [LAUGHING CONTINUES]
[♪♪♪]
[SARAH CHUCKLING]
[EXHALES, GASPS]
[OLIVER AND SARAH LAUGHING]
[STIFLED SOB]
[SOBS, SNIFFLES]
SARAH: I'll protect you.
[♪♪♪]
[MUSIC FADES]